Guide to the Office of the Dean, Washington Square College and Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science 1929-1984 (Bulk 1951-1980) RG.19
New York University Archives
- Series II: Additional Dean's Files
  - Planning Board, 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227100 0
  - Office for Planning and Development, 1967-1979 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Director of Planning and Supervising Architect, 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Portuguese Chair, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Posters, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Post-Graduate WSC Questionnaire, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Pre-Law Program, 1973-1975 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Pre-Law Society, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Pre-Med Program: Statistics, Memos etc., 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Pre-Medical Scholarships, 1966-1968 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Pre-Med, Pre-Dent, Pre-Law Scholarships and Awards, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Pre-Veterinary Society, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - President, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - President, 1963-1976 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Promotion and Tenure Departmental Machinary, 1965-1977 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Promotional Brochures, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Provost, 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - President's Councils, 1965-1969 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Presidential Citation, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Presidential Convocation, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Presidential Reception, 1964-1968 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Presidential Search Committee, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Pre-Teaching Programs, 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - NYU Programs Abroad, 1969-1976 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Psychology, 1967-1970 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Psychology, 1971-1975 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Publications, 1969-1977 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Publications Sub-Committee, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Publicity, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Public Interest Research Group (PIRG), 1973 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Public Relations, 1964-1975 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Public Relations Courses, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Misc. "Q", 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Misc. "R", 1964-1974 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Mabel Rabkin, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - AB/DDS Radiation Biology, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Race Relations, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Rank Order List, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Reading Institute, 1964-1965 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Reading Period, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Recommendations/Students, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Recommendations/Non-Student, Non-Faculty, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Committee on Recommendations to Medical and Dental Schools, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Recommedentations to Medical School, 1963-1974 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Student Records, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Recorder, 1968-1976 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Graduate Count Recorder, 1971-1978 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Recreational Facilities, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Regents College Teaching Fellowships, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Regents Graduate Fellowship Programs, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Regents Scholarships, 1962-1967 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Registrar General, 1963-1974 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Registrar Enrollment Estimates, 1971-1977 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Room Assignments, Registration Facilities and Processes, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Non-Preregistrants, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Pre-Registration, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Registration, 1967-1975 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Registration by Mail, 1964-1967 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Interim Reports of Registration, 1968-1975 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Registration of Undergraduate Programs for Degrees, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Registration Procedures, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Registration Statistics (Recorder), 1967-1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227101 8
  - Religion, 1967-1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - The New Republic, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Republic Steel (Annual Report), 1974 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Request by Students to See Records, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Requests For, 1966-1970 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Classified Research, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Funds for Research, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Sidney Roth Office of Research Services, 1967-1976 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Estimates of the Projected Sponsored Research and Training Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Sponsored Research and Training Programs Manual, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Residences, 1963-1976 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Residence Hall Affairs Enrollment Complaints, etc., 1973-1976 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Reston Lecture, 1962-1968 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Chi-Reston Crisis, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Resumes, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Institute of Retail Management, 1963-1971 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Retailing Career Day, 1963-1968 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Outgoing Interviews - Student Retention, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Rhodes Scholarhip, 1963-1973 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Brooks Roberts, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Robinson, Robert, 1965-1968 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Romance Languages, 1966-1975 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Rome Summer Session, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Delmor Schwarz Reception for Mr. Raphael Rudnick, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Air Force ROTC: Metropolitan Area, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Misc. "S", 1963-1966 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - SDS Posters, 1960-1970 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - S & H Foundation, 1967-1974 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Safety, 1968-1974 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Salaries, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Sample Letters, 1963-1979 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Stanely Saplin - Assistant to President, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Saturday, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Saturday Review, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Sawhill Dinner, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Schnitzer, Henry R. UC Alumnus, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Committee on University Scholars, 1965-1967 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Scholarships, 1965-1967 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Committee on Scholarship Awards, 1965-1970 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Scholarship Funds for Class Entering in Feb. 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Committee on Scholarship Standards, 1967-1974 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Science, Interdiscliplinary, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Science Library, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Search Committee for New Dean, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - FAS Search Committee CVs of Possible Deans, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Secretarial Clerical Needs, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Mobutu Sese Seko - Distinguished Lecturer Series, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Seminar Method, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Senate Faculty Council, 1969-1976 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Senators, 1968-1972 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - "Senior Drag", 1972-1974 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Senior Reception, 1968-1974 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Sentiment, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Shakespeare Scholarship Contest, 1963-1966 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Dean Siegel, 1970-1975 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Sigma, 1965-1967 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Singer Company Foundation, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Slavic, 1967-1975 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Howard K. Smith Lecture, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - School of Social Work Memorandums - Program Activities, 1975-1978 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Society for the Libraries, 1964-1969 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Sociology, 1967-1975 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - Max Solorsy, 1967-1973 (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - NYU in Spain, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227102 6
  - NYU in Spain, 1963-1979 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - NYU in Spain Contract, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Spanish Portuguese, 1970-1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - NYU in Spain, 1963-1979 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Sponsored Programs, 1975-1978 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Sponsored Programs, 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Sponsored Programs Tally Sheets, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Student Attrition, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Square Journal, 1964-1968 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - The NYU Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - "Staff Newsletter", 1969 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Staff Relations, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Stamm, James R., 1965-1969 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Standing Committee of the Senate and Senate Rules, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Standing Committees, 1968-1974 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Starr, Wilmarth H., 1963-1969 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - State Education Dept, 1974-1976 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - State Education Dept/International Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Steering Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Sterling Forest, 1963-1965 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Sterling Forest Music Festival, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Strike Correspondence, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Strike - Maintence Workers Feb-March 1971 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Students, 1966-1969 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Student Activities, 1967-1971 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Washington Square College Student Council, 1964-1972 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - WSUC Student Council, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Student Directory, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Student Faculty Forum, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Student Initiated Courses, 1973-1977 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Job Opportunities for Students, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Commission on Student Life, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Student Life, 1964-1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227103 4
  - Committee on Student Life, 1965-1976 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Student Lounge Plans, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Student Marketing Plan (Confidential), 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - WSC Student Partcipation, 1968-1971 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Student Posters, 1970-1972 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Students Privacy Rights, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Student Projections, 1973-1975 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - SDS 1960's, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Study Group on Advisement and Counseling, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Stuyvesant VOICE, 1974-1978 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Suarez de Puga, 1963-1966 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Summer Institute, 1968-1974 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Mailing List for Summer School, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Organization of Summer School, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Summer Session/ADS, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Summer Session, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Summer Session, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Summer Session, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Summer Session 1976 Advertising (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Summer Session Courses Outline, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1972-1975 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Sunrise Semester Fanmail, 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Swimming, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Symposium in the Arts and Sciences, 1963-1965 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - KLM Mrs. Tabor, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Take Me Home Rickshaw Poems by Contemporary Poets of Bangladesh, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Tamiment Institute Library, 1963-1965 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Taskforce, 1972-1976 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Commission on Teacher Education, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Commission on Teacher Education, 1964-1972 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Teachers Ed. CTE Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Teaching Loads, 1963-1968 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - 1976 TARA Telephone Routes and Codes (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - David Teitelbaum, 1972-1976 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Commission to Study Tenure (University of Utah), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Tenure, 1960-1979 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Tenure, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - "La Tertulia Latina", 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Texas Instruments Foundation Founders Prize, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - New York Theological Institute Consortium, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - The Third World in Global Context by Prof. Hsiung, 1972-1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227104 2
  - Virgil Thomson Music, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - "Ticker", 1969 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Time Shortened Degree Programs - California State College Questionnaire, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Oswald Tippo, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Tisch Hall, 1968-1973 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Tokyo Scholarship, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Toven, 1963-1969 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Town Hall, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Transfer Students, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer, 1969-1975 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Trustees, 1968-1977 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Turkish, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Tuition Fees, 1965-1974 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Tuition Remission, 1964-1970 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Tutorial Group, 1963-1967 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Tutoring Program, 1965-1972 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - High School/College Articulation Program Undergraduate Commission, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate Planning, 1974-1976 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Planning, 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Uniform Time Modules Proposal, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Union, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Union Election May 15, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Union Posters, Elections, etc., 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - United Nations Association of New York, 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - University, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - University College, 1967-1970 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - University College, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - University College, 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - University College, 1972-1974 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - The University and the City, 1964-1966 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on the Use of University Facilities, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - University of the State of New York, 1966-1975 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - University Without Walls, 1969-1971 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - University Without Walls - London, 1971-1974 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - University Without Walls, 1972-1974 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - University Without Walls, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - University Without Walls (Antioch), 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Urban Health Affairs, 1968-1971 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Urban Studies (Landmarks Scholars Program - Fine Arts), 1974 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Urban Studies, 1965-1970 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Center for Urban Studies, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Urban University, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Immanuel Velikovsky, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - The American Institute for Verdi Studies Newsletter, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Veterans Recruitment, 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Vice President Armstrong, 1955-1958 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Vice President Berezin, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Vice President Campbell, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - Vice President De Capriles, 1968-1974 (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - Vice President David Robinson, 1967-1975 (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Vice President Williams, 1962-1967 (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - "The Villager", 1974 (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - Violet Fraternity Council, 1963-1967 (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - Virginia State College at Norfolk, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - Visiting Scholars, 1964-1973 (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - Visiting Students Program, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227105 9
  - Visitors Program State Dept Bureau of Education and Cultural Affairs, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Voice Party, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Professor Von Guerard, 1963-1972 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Voting Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Wagreich, 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Ingo Walter, GBA, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Reports from Washington, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square Committee, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square Review, 1965-1972 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square Village, 1963-1976 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Watt Lecture, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - A Way with Words Conference, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Curriculum for Weekend College, 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Rene Wellek, 1964-1965 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Whiteman, 1967-1971 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Who's Who Recommendations and Info, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Wide World Lecture Bureau, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Wilderness Workshop, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Mabel Williamson, 1968-1973 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - RBW Chairman Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Dean Winder, 1969-1976 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Wisconsin Universities UN Seminar, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Withdrawals, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Women, 1970-1973 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Work-Study Program, 1969-1971 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Association of Women Students, 1964-1966 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship, 1968-1971 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - World Microfilms Publications, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Writing Center, 1964-1969 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Xerox, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Xerox College Publishing, 1971-1974 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Yearbook, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Thomas Brophy - Sunrise Semester, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227106 7
  - Sunrise Semester, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Sunrise Semester Contract, 1963-1978 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Sunrise Semester Course Distribution, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Sunrise Semester Course in Islam, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Sunrise Semester Funding, 1972-1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Sunrise Semester Fundraising, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Sunrise Semester Grant Proposals, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Sunrise Semester History, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Sunrise Semester in Other Colleges, 1967-1979 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Sunrise Semester Job Descriptions, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Sunrise Semester Misc., 1971-1978 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Sunrise Semester Past Courses, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Sunrise Semester Publicity, 1978-1981 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Sunrise Semester Sawhill Course, 1978-1981 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Sunrise Semester New Courses, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Sunrise Semester New Funding Ideas, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Sunrise Semester News Articles, 1971-1980 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Sunrise Semester Amy Ostrawer Research Consultant, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Sunrise Semester Ideas for Courses, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Sunrise Semester Funding, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Sunrise Semester CBS Contracts and Agreements, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Sunrise Semester Courses, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Sunrise Semester Operating Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Sunrise Semster Womenand Men in Changing Society, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Sunrise Semster Bills, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1978-1979 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Sunrise Semester Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Sunrise Semester Curriculum Committee, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Sunrise Semester ECRs, 1978-1979 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Sunrise Semester Ancient Egyptian Art, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - FAS Budget Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Security Committee, Information about Members, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Secutiry Committee: Minutes and Agendas, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Security Committee, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Security Input Firm Faculty, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Security Protection Services: Reports to Edward Schnell and Staff Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227107 5
  - Security Committee: UCSL Subcommittee on Security, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Security Committee: Senate Discussion of Security Committee Report, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Security Committee: Final Report, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Security: Auxiliary Police Information, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Security, 1979-1981 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Security Committee: Minutes From Zone Visits, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - NYU In The News, January-February, 1982-1983 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - NYU In The News, November-December, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - NYU In The News, Fall, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - NYU In The News, March-April, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Policy and Planning, 1977-1982 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Planning/Long Range, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Martin Bernstein Hall, 1969-1973 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Professor Andre Beaumont (Deceased), 1974 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Dean's Meetings-Spring/Summer, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Dean's Meetings-Fall, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Dean's Meetings: Time and Effort Reporting (Faculty Policies), 1980 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Dean's Meetings-Spring/Summer, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Item, Joseph C. Wilson Award Committee, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda: Space Management, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Items-Faculty Staffing Policies and Procedure, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Items-Telecommunications-Telephone, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Dean's Meeting-Animal Welfare Regulations, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Dean's Meeting-Implications of the Bakke Decision, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Items: Capital Budgeting, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Dean's Meetings-Spring/Summer, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Dean's Meetings-Fall, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Item, Time Modules, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Item, NYU 150th Anniversary, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Dean's Meeting (Retirement Age), 1979 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Items, Early Retirement and Individual Status Agreement, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Park, Joseph H. Honor Society, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Medical Center-Financial Report, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Dean's Meetings, Fall, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Dean's Meetings, Spring, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227108 3
  - Dean's Meetings, Fall, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Development Charitable Gift-Annuity, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Development Donations, 1975-1978 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Development, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Development Leadership Campaign, 1976-1979 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Senate, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Senate, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Senate, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Senate, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Senate, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Senate-Rules of Procedure, undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - GSAS-MA and MS Degrees, 1972-1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227109 1
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 13)